A Guide to the Virginia Department of Treasury, Division of Unclaimed Property, 1822-1991
Library of Virginia
- Records - Accession 52072, 1862-1988., Extent: 17 boxes. (Box 61-77)
  - Lot 6135 - Papers of Raymond W. Cavanagh, Jr., 1975-1976. (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Lot 6136 - Papers of James and Mae Cheatham, 1970-1978. (Box 70, Folder 16)
  - Lot 6137 - Papers of Michael Christopher, 1973-1974. (Box 70, Folder 17)
  - Lot 6141 - Papers of Sarah and Joe Fitzgerald, 1981. (Box 70, Folder 18)
  - Lot 6142 - Papers of Dennis Stemmle, 1974. (Box 70, Folder 19)
  - Lot 6144 - Papers of Clay Hall, 1973-1974. (Box 70, Folder 20)
  - Lot 6146 - Papers of Martha McCullough, 1977-1978. (Box 70, Folder 21)
  - Lot 6147 - Papers of Helen E. Morris, 1968-1973. (Box 70, Folder 22)
  - Lot 6148 - Papers of Jessica G. Nelson, 1977. (Box 70, Folder 23)
  - Lot 6149 - Papers of George Nicholas, 1975-1976. (Box 70, Folder 24)
  - Lot 6151 - Papers of Brady and Mary Rackley, 1964-1971. (Box 70, Folder 25)
  - Lot 6153 - Papers of Christopher Rheuby, 1973-1975. (Box 70, Folder 26)
  - Lot 6155 - Papers of James and Frances Ross, 1977-1978. (Box 70, Folder 27)
  - Lot 6156 - Papers of John and Gloria Ross, 1963. (Box 70, Folder 28)
  - Lot 6158 - Papers of Jerry and Phyllis Simpkins, 1971-1976. (Box 70, Folder 29)
  - Lot 6176 - Papers of Daniel J. Browne, 1987-1988. (Box 70, Folder 30)
  - Lot 6177 - Papers of Karen Harrison, 1981-1988. (Box 70, Folder 31)
  - Lot 6219 - Papers of Lawrence and Susan Troy, 1971-1975. (Box 70, Folder 32)
  - Lot 6224 - Papers of James and Brenda Zettervall, 1977. (Box 70, Folder 33)
  - Lot 6261 - Papers of Edmund Barnett, 1967-1971. (Box 70, Folder 34)
  - Lot 6262 - Papers of Clifford Bishop, 1965. (Box 70, Folder 35)
  - Lot 6263 - Papers of Albert A. Branch, 1915-1978. (Box 70, Folder 36)
  - Lot 6264 - Papers of Anne Butcher, 1971-1972. (1 of 3) (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Lot 6264 - Papers of Anne Butcher, 1972-1974. (2 of 3) (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Lot 6264 - Papers of Anne Butcher, 1919-1973. (3 of 3) (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Lot 6268 - Papers of Timothy R. Knowlton, 1975. (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Lot 6269 - Papers of Ann Clements, 1967-1983. (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Lot 6271 - Papers of Loretha Dodson, 1982. (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Lot 6272 - Papers of William F. Douthwaite, III, 1973-1974. (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Lot 6273 - Papers of Donald S. Drumwright, 1967-1974. (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Lot 6276 - Papers of James M. Giovannini, 1973. (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Lot 6277 - Papers of Kathleen Golz, 1972. (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Lot 6279 - Papers of Nancy Howells Grant, n.d. (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Lot 6280 - Papers of Shirley Green, 1957-1976. (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Lot 6281 - Papers of Paul D. Harkrader, 1911-1950. (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Lot 6283 - Papers of Brenda and Lee Jenkins, 1979. (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Lot 6284 - Papers of Robert Lee Johnson, 1961-1962. (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Lot 6286 - Papers of Glendon Cales, 1967-1969. (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Lot 6287 - Papers of Sheila Lewis, 1978-1981. (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Lot 6288 - Papers of James and Irene Lewis, 1971-1974. (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Lot 6292 - Papers of Henry C. Mitchell, 1982. (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Lot 6295 - Papers of Victor Meleski, 1976. (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - Lot 6297 - Papers of George Osipovas, 1972. (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Lot 6299 - Papers of Esperanza Liffet Paez, 1964-1980. (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - Lot 6300 - Papers of Jane or Ann Pannell, 1965. (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Lot 6302 - Papers of Judy Pomeroy, 1972. (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Lot 6303 - Papers of Ted Prothero, 1934-1965. (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Lot 6307 - Papers of Anthony M. Rey, 1969-1980. (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Lot 6309 - Papers of Dora or Enid Roop, 1964. (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Lot 6311 - Papers of Robert Sanders, 1963-1971. (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Lot 6316 - Papers of Jean S. Spitzer, 1967-1979. (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Lot 6319 - Papers of Alan Taylor, 1975. (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Lot 6320 - Papers of Edward or David Thomas, 1981. (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Lot 6322 - Papers of Kenneth and Valory Thompson, 1973. (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Lot 6323 - Papers of Gary M. Freakle, 1977. (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Lot 6325 - Papers of Cline H. Walter, 1964. (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Lot 6329 - Papers of Otis Whisnant, 1979. (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Lot 6332 - Papers of Kenneth Wright, 1973-1976. (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Lot 6333 - Papers of Mary Northington, 1965-1976. (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Lot 6338 - Papers of Robert and Patricia McCloud, 1975. (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Lot 6339 - Papers of Frederick B. and Mary Dodson Mowry, 1974. (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - Lot 6344 - Papers of Sovran Bank, Misc., 1922-1977. (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - Lot 6348 - Papers of William J. Apple, 1963-1966. (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - Lot 6349 - Papers of Willie Arps, Jr., 1966-1972. (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - Lot 6351 - Papers of Romell and James Askew, 1958-1982. (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - Lot 6352 - Papers of Robert Aulthouse, 1946-1973. (Box 72, Folder 22)
  - Lot 6355 - Papers of Gail and Russell Barnes, 1964-1971. (Box 72, Folder 23)
  - Lot 6358 - Papers of Gerald and Ellen Ziegler, 1974. (Box 72, Folder 24)
  - Lot 6359 - Papers of Karen F. Bolle, 1973-1976. (Box 72, Folder 25)
  - Lot 6362 - Papers of Katrene C. Boyette, 1973. (Box 72, Folder 26)
  - Lot 6363 - Papers of R. Bradley and C. E. Fitchett, 1972-1976. (Box 72, Folder 27)
  - Lot 6364 - Papers of Barbara A. Bristow, 1967-1976. (Box 72, Folder 28)
  - Lot 6368 - Papers of Edward and Karen Brown, 1973-1974. (Box 72, Folder 29)
  - Lot 6375 - Papers of Maxine Carter, 1977-1978. (Box 72, Folder 30)
  - Lot 6384 - Papers of James Lee Coleman, Jr., 1963. (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Lot 6386 - Papers of Betty Lou Collier, 1924-1988. (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Lot 6387 - Papers of William W. Combow, 1951-1966. (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Lot 6392 - Papers of Betty J. Smartz, 1970-1977. (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Lot 6393 - Papers of William and Jevene Dixon, 1971-1974. (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Lot 6394 - Papers of Ollie Dodd, 1909-1972. (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Lot 6399 - Papers of Mary A. Ellis, 1973. (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Lot 6401 - Papers of Virginia Evans and Gloria Podruchny, 1955-1978. (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Lot 6410 - Papers of Edward Frye III, 1933-1965. (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Lot 6411 - Papers of Fuyuko Shinoda Fergeson, 1975-1976. (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Lot 6414 - Papers of Arline and Cheryl Gales, 1932-1975. (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Lot 6415 - Papers of Evelyn M. Garvin, 1954. (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Lot 6416 - Papers of William and Debra Gary, 1958-1978. (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Lot 6419 - Papers of Ronald Gentry, 1974. (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Lot 6421 - Papers of Nicholas J. Gormley, 1933-1974. (1 of 2) (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Lot 6421 - Papers of Nicholas J. Gormley, 1933-1974. (2 of 2) (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Lot 6523 - Papers of Nicholas and Nancy Gormley, 1956-1971. (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Lot 6425 - Papers of Stan and Pat Green, 1962-1976. (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Lot 6427 - Papers of Raymond Gut, 1976-1977. (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Lot 6429 - Papers of Sally Hamilton, 1978. (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Lot 6430 - Papers of John and Barbara Hare, 1964-1971. (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Lot 6431 - Papers of John A. Hart, 1976. (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Lot 6432 - Papers of Floyd and Martha Hayes, 1936-1970. (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Lot 6433 - Papers of Mrs. W. S. Henderson, 1894-1960. (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Lot 6446 - Papers of Thomas C. Joyce, 1972. (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Lot 6447 - Papers of Brenda Moore Keith, 1972-1976. (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Lot 6448 - Papers of Martha Henderson Rudder Terry/Keller, 1936-1974. (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Lot 6449 - Papers of Theodore Kramer, 1959-1973. (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Lot 6451 - Papers of Robbin E. Lawrence, 1973. (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Lot 6453 - Papers of Carole Lawrence, 1967-1973. (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Lot 6457 - Papers of Carrera Ludwig, 1978. (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Lot 6460 - Papers of John and Letty Marshall, 1963-1978. (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Lot 6460 - Papers of Ronnie McCall, 1972. (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - Lot 6461 - Papers of Otis Melvin, 1943-1969. (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - Lot 6464 - Papers of Morgan Merrill, 1980-1981. (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - Lot 6465 - Papers of Mary R. Moore, 1957-1978. (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - Lot 6466 - Papers of Allyn Morgan III, 1974. (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - Lot 6470 - Papers of Douglas and Debra Murphy, 1973-1975. (Box 74, Folder 21)
  - Lot 6471 - Papers of Arnold Murray and D. Roberson, 1966-1972. (Box 74, Folder 22)
  - Lot 6473 - Papers of Albert F. Namon, 1974. (Box 74, Folder 23)
  - Lot 6474 - Papers of Frances D. Newton, 1966-1978. (Box 74, Folder 24)
  - Lot 6476 - Papers of Selena Nobles, 1973. (Box 74, Folder 25)
  - Lot 6478 - Papers of G. Papadopoulus, 1976-1977. (Box 74, Folder 26)
  - Lot 6479 - Papers of Hazel Natalie Parker, 1977-1978. (Box 74, Folder 27)
  - Lot 6481 - Papers of Lenore Parker, 1970. (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Lot 6483 - Papers of Darrell and Jackie Payne, 1971-1974. (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Lot 6484 - Papers of Timothy Pearson, 1980. (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Lot 6489 - Papers of Herbert and Marie Quick, 1899-1965. (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Lot 6490 - Papers of Edgar T. Justice, 1965. (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Lot 6492 - Papers of Lawrence V. Robertson, 1975-1977. (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Lot 6496 - Papers of Robert and Meredith Ryder, 1908-1979. (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Lot 6498 - Papers of Kenneth R. Saunders, 1974. (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Lot 6499 - Papers of William T. Schmidt, 1948-1978. (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Lot 6506 - Papers of Wanda Herring Shister, 1955. (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Lot 6507 - Papers of Irene Short, 1974. (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Lot 6508 - Papers of A. E. Simpson, 1938-1978. (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Lot 6510 - Papers of C. W. Davis, 1967-1968. (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Lot 6511 - Papers of Randall Stidham, 1976. (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Lot 6512 - Papers of Boyd E. Tankersley, 1971. (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Lot 6516 - Papers of Creed Tompkins, 1967-1968. (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Lot 6518 - Papers of Reynaldo A. Vicerra, 1977. (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Lot 6520 - Papers of Norma J. Vickers, 1965-1967. (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Lot 6522 - Papers of Peggy Ann Walker, 1976-1977. (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Lot 6523 - Papers of Robert and Linda Walker, 1973. (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Lot 6524 - Papers of Russell C. Walker, 1974. (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Lot 6525 - Papers of Shara Waller, 1974-1977. (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - Lot 6529 - Papers of Anthony B. Williams, 1963. (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - Lot 6531 - Papers of Alice M. Wilson, 1948-1974. (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Lot 6534 - Papers of Ida Wilson, 1969. (Box 75, Folder 25)
  - Lot 6535 - Papers of Jake and Violet Wolfe, 1953-1978. (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - Lot 6537 - Papers of Woods Unlimited, 1979. (Box 75, Folder 27)
  - Lot 6538 - Papers of Judith O. Allison, 1977. (Box 75, Folder 28)
  - Lot 6540 - Papers of Ludell Crawford, 1971-1972. (Box 75, Folder 29)
  - Lot 6543 - Papers of J. Kindley, 1970-1973. (Box 75, Folder 30)
  - Lot 6544 - Papers of Richard L. Pennock, 1968. (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - Lot 6545 - Papers of Tina Swain, 1959-1981. (Box 75, Folder 32)
  - Lot 6551 - Papers of Daniel Boyle, 1976-1977. (Box 75, Folder 33)
  - Lot 6559 - Papers of Herbert L. Aman, 1967-1968. (Box 75, Folder 34)
  - Lot 6561 - Papers of James M. Guiliano, 1951-1973. (Box 75, Folder 35)
  - Lot 6863 - Papers of Carl Coffman, 1975-1976. (1 of 5) (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Lot 6863 - Papers of Carl Coffman, Jan.-Feb. 1976. (2 of 5) (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Lot 6863 - Papers of Carl Coffman, Mar.-Apr. 1976. (3 of 5) (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Lot 6863 - Papers of Carl Coffman, May 1976. (4 of 5) (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Lot 6863 - Papers of Carl Coffman, June-Aug. 1976, n.d. (5 of 5) (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Lot 6889 - Papers of Barbara Grose, 1976-1977. (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Lot 6890 - Papers of Rogers D. Jones, 1960-1973. (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Lot 6894 - Papers of Jay Ball, n.d. (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Lot 6895 - Papers of Mary Burcher, 1954-1978. (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Lot 6896 - Papers of Daniel Westate, 1940-1971. (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Lot 6897 - Papers of Normal and Donald Robinson, 1970-1974. (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Lot 6901 - Papers of Floyd and Sandra Robistow, 1978. (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Lot 6902 - Papers of William Strawn, 1973. (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Lot 6910 - Papers of David Harrell, Jr., 1977. (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Lot 6914 - Papers of William Clark, n.d. (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Lot 6916 - Papers of Barbara McLean Furr, 1976. (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Lot 6918 - Papers of Martha and Thomas Hayes, 1955-1977. (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Lot 6923 - Papers of Stanley C. Anthony, 1979. (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Lot 7288 - Papers of Charles Armistead, Jr., n.d. (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Lot 7388 - Papers of Janice E. Racel, 1939-1971. (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Lot 7389 - Papers of Edward L. Racel, 1958-1963. (Box 77, Folder 15)
- Records - Accession 52086, 1862-1988., Extent: boxes. (Box 1-)
  - Lot 8217 - Papers of Marsha Hubbard Leake,1974. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Lot 8218 - Papers of Douglas A. Lettow,ca. 1970-1980. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Lot 8224 - Papers of Daniel L. McElroy,1974-1975. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Lot 8227 - Papers of Foster D. McGarity,1975-1979. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Lot 8228 - Papers of Constance McGill,1964-1979. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Lot 8231 - Papers of Tony J. and Rose Nicholas,1970-1971. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Lot 8230 - Papers of Nancy J. or Albert J. Miller,1976. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Lot 8232 - Papers of Melba W. Payne,ca. 1970-1990. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Lot 8234 - Papers of Barbara and Edward Pyne,1941. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Lot 8239 - Papers of Wallace R. Rogers,1977. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Lot 8249 - Papers of Thomas Wine,1973-1976. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Lot 8250 - Papers of Jeannette Louise Wallen Zitzewitz,ca. 1945-1970. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Lot 8255 - Papers of the Peoples Bank of White Stone, Virginia,1932-1964. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Lot 8256 - Papers of James Nottingham and Sadie Nottingham,1964-1970. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Lot 8259 - Papers of Peoples Bank of White Stone, Virginia,1932. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Lot 8260 - Papers of Peoples Bank of White Stone, Virginia,1922-1960. (Box 1, Folder 16)